SAVANA ALDEN

FRONTEND TECH LEAD

SKILLS

HTML/CSS Javascript Handlebars React & Vue Github SVN Craft CMS

LESS TECHNICAL

Sketch Adobe XD Photoshop Illustrator After Effects

ABOUT

Savana is a frontend web developer with an eye for design. She is also passionate about animation and creating a user friendly and accessible web experience. She is a project lead and enjoys finding creative solutions to technical problems. In her spare time she enjoys drawing, travelling, reading, and talking in the third person.

EDUCATION

North Idaho College

Web Design AAS SEP 2013 - DEC 2016

EXPERIENCE

Critical Mass

Tech Lead 2023 - PRESENT
Senior Developer 2022 - 2023
Developer 2020 - 2022

Client: Apple

Created a dynamic and organized system to execute projects more efficiently. Leads projects and oversees the deployment. Works on multiple teams with using various tech stacks. Supervises other developers on projects. Solo and team projects. Works on multiple campaigns simultaneously. Works on tight deadlines with proficiency. Executes prototypes of designers' visions using only HTML & CSS.

14Four

Frontend Developer SEP 2018 - AUG 2020

Partial client list: Svedka Vodka, Quaker Oats, Adidas, Ruffles, Constellation Brands, Mountain Dew, AT&T

Worked with Craft CMS to create websites so clients can maintain the content while the frontend stays unique in it's design and functionality. Created single page applications with React and Vue. Worked with a team on multiple different canvas-based web games integrating React or Vue with my responisibilites involving the UI.